#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sergio-cordero-b0b52516 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

**UML** 

SQL

C++

## Languages

Portuguese (Professional Working)
English (Professional Working)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Oracle DBA

# Sergio Cordero

Senior Developer C++ at Endava Argentina

## Summary

I have been working as C++ Senior Developer and C Senior Developer for more than 20 years switching between both language VB Developer for 2 years

Java

PHP

Perl

SQL Server

Oracle

**ProC** 

C# Developer

Unix/Linux

Specialties: I have more than 20 years of experience switching between C and C++

Application Developer, in a wide variety of business (POS, Petroleum, Energy, Telecomunications, Payments, Video recorder) applications. Particularly interested in client/server applications with C++ and relational database design using Oracle,and/or MS-SQL Server.

# Experience

Endava

Senior Developer C++

April 2021 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Buenos Aires, Buenos Aires Province, Argentina

Working in SafeFleet project, managing video records Application developed in C++ and C#

**Tecnotree Corporation** 

Sr. Software Developer

October 2016 - April 2021 (4 years 7 months)

Greater Buenos Aires, Argentina

Telecom industry, C++, C Developer,

Page 1 of 3

Solaris,

Linux,

Signaling, Diameter Protocol

Sybase as Data Base

Worldline Global

**Developer Analyst** 

June 2016 - October 2016 (5 months)

**Developer Analyst** 

C++, C Developer

Linux, embebed Linux

POS

The principal main task is to developing for POS, Contactless Card, Auto Service Terminal.

Redknee / Orga Systems

**DEVELOPER CONSULTANT** 

April 2011 - May 2016 (5 years 2 months)

**Buenos Aires** 

Developer Consultant P2

C++, C Developer

Java

Oracle

**XML** 

Unix/Linux

I'm Working on Pre Pay TIM Brasil (currently)

I worked on Migration TPA Argentina

I Worked on Pre Pay ENTEL Chile

The main task is analysis, design, and implementation on Classic product

Capgemini

Solution Designer C++

December 2009 - April 2011 (1 year 5 months)

Argentina, Buenos Aires

Solution Designer level 2 for ENDESA (SPAIN)

C++ Senior Developer, XML, UML, SQL Server, Oracle, ProC

Working with Energy Applications, using Ilog IDE of IBM

Gilbarco Veeder Root

Senior Developer C++

September 2005 - December 2009 (4 years 4 months)

Page 2 of 3

#### **Buenos Aires**

C, C++ Developer

I worked with Oil Petroleum industry software.

Design of new aplication and maintenance of existent aplication

The tecnology used was SQL, C#, XML, VB, UML.

Manage of handset, pump, crind, etc.

Invel Latinoamericana S.A.

Developer C++

August 2000 - August 2005 (5 years 1 month)

C Developer for 5 years, with realtional database (MSSQL Server)

Btrieve data base.

I worked in Retail software for Supermarket.

Manage of fiscal and no fiscal printers such as Epson, IBM, NCR, etc. POS

## Education

Universidad Blas Pascal

Licenciatura en Informatica, Computer · (1997 - 2000)

Universidad Blas Pascal

Licentiate degree, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services · (1997 - 2000)

Universidad Blas Pascal

Licentiate degree Computer SCience, Computer Science · (1997 - 2000)

# Activity

11/01/2023, Viewed by Magali Feintuch